

const quizData = [
    {
        question: "Question 1",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 0
    },{
        question: "Question 2",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 1
    },{
        question: "Question 3",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 2
    },{
        question: "Question 4",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 3
    },{
        question: "Question 5",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 0
    },{
        question: "Question 6",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 1
    },{
        question: "Question 7",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 2
    },{
        question: "Question 8",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 3
    },{
        question: "Question 9",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 0
    },{
        question: "Question 10",
        options: ["Select 1", "Select 2", "Select 3", "Select 4"],
        AnswerIndex: 1
    }
]

export default quizData;